Two people
Двое сюда
Move this inside
занесите это внутрь
Carefully
Осторожнее
Please come in
Пожалуйста проходите
Hurry
Быстрее
Why did we stop here?
Почему остановились здесь
Careful, please come in
Осторожно прошу
Blocked outside, can't get through
Впереди всё перекрыто
I'll clear a path
Я расчищу путь
Let's walk
Пройдём пешком
Prince of Ning
Принц Нин
General Zu
Генерал Цзу
Please come in
Пожалуйста проходите
Prince of Ning's meaning
Намёк принца Нина
I understand
я понял
If the general has difficulties
Генерал если у вас в столице
In the capital or elsewhere
или гделибо ещё возникнут трудности
You can directly send someone to inform me
дайте знать
I will
я непременно
Do my utmost to help
помогу
Thank you
Благодарю
What a grand gesture
Какой же размах
Move faster
Пошевеливайтесь
Don't block others from coming and going
не мешайте проходу
Second brother is here too
О и младший брат пожаловал
Greetings to Prince of Jin
Приветствую принца Цзиня
General Zu
Генерал Цзу
Elder brother
Брат
Why
Почему
Did you walk here yourself?
сам пешком
I blocked the way ahead
Наверное изза того что мы перекрыли дорогу
If you have anything to move
Если чтото нужно перенести
I'll have them help you move it
велю им помочь
No need to trouble elder brother
Не стоит утруждать тебя брат